<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on NLP Ventures</title>
    <link>https://develop.d2pru1nc16cre5.amplifyapp.com/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on NLP Ventures</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 14:33:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://develop.d2pru1nc16cre5.amplifyapp.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark French</title>
      <link>https://develop.d2pru1nc16cre5.amplifyapp.com/about/mark-french/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 14:33:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://develop.d2pru1nc16cre5.amplifyapp.com/about/mark-french/</guid>
      <description>Mark French has created and operated disruptive business innovations in the sports, consumer goods, media and technology industries. As the recipient of three ‘40 Under 40 Awards’ in three separate business sectors, Mark has proven that his passion, creativity, leadership and entrepreneurial skill sets drive sustainable growth across industries. Mark is an active investor, board member and advisor for companies that share his drive to disrupt and innovate in Sports, Media and Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No-Look Pass Ventures</title>
      <link>https://develop.d2pru1nc16cre5.amplifyapp.com/about/about-nlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 14:33:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://develop.d2pru1nc16cre5.amplifyapp.com/about/about-nlp/</guid>
      <description>NLP Ventures is a hands-on operational accelerator and partner for portfolio companies in the Sports, Entertainment, and Technology sectors. Led by serial entrepreneur and investor, Mark French, NLP Ventures is an active innovation and activation engine comprised of experienced hands-on builders with expertise in product development, brand building, strategic partnerships, M&amp;A, disruptive marketing, and talent acquisition.
We serve as a founder&#39;s most trusted teammate and an investor&#39;s strongest defender. As an active board member, we provide industry expertise, strategic direction, along with access to NLP Ventures world class partners, including:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>